my three words concept from chris broger.
now there's three words every single year.
i choose to work on. so actually it's three areas. i choose to work on. i learned this from one of my virtual mentor, named chris broke.
and he actually developed it.
i think that's like 20 years ago.
i only discovered his way a few years back, but i truly, truly liked it.
because before, my three words, i'm using a special goal each year to have a special area i need to work.
i said, a person.
one year i worked on a slow to judge, quick to love when i meet different people.
and then another year i'm working on maybe lessons.
more. another year i'm working on to learn the new technology more.
another year i learned what was set up the the goal for myself is to how i can learn from the young people they're 20 years younger than me
but since i read the book of bruce groot and
is broken.
and also read his blogs and regarding this my three words each year.
and i really, really like this idea.
2024ers minds learn work.
is aware.
here.
so if you wanted to know the meanings of that and how to apply it, actually wrote a blog link.
probably can find that one.
just remember.